...to give up?
（レム）
諦めるんですか？
助ける方法は ほかには…
Is there no other way to save...
...suppose not.
The rest is in your hands now.
（ベアトリス）
あとは
お前の好きにするがいいのよ
I swear...
（レム）必ず 助けます
I'll save you.
（ナツキ･スバル）
また見知らぬ天井
Another unfamiliar ceiling.
イッテ！
Ow!
かろうじて命を拾って
治療されたあとってことか
So they barely managed to save my life, and these scars are proof of that.
Emilia...
エミリア
I guess now I owe her yet another debt.
俺はまた この子に
借りを作っちまったのか
（パック）それはどうかな？
（スバル）ん…
I don't know about that.
This time, you produced results equal
to the effort she invested,
今回の君は 労力に見合った
成果を上げてるから―
so I doubt Lia will think of it as a debt.
リアも 貸し借りがどうとかなんて
思わないんじゃないかな
Puck...
パック
Good morning, Subaru.
やっ おはようスバル
You say I produced results equal to her efforts,
見合った成果 つったけど―
正直 俺は森で犬どもに
ガブガブされたところから―
but I don't remember anything after I got nommed on by those dogs in the forest.
記憶がねえんだが…
"Nommed on"? That's a cute way to put it.
ガブガブってかわいい表現だね
But it was more like:
でも 実際は―
Munch, gobble, snarf, chew,
chomp, snap, crunch!
ムシャ ボリ グシャ ブチ
ブチ ミチ バリ ブシャー！
って感じだったよ
Or something similar.
By the sound of that,
it's a miracle I'm not dead right now.
その効果音だと
間違いなく死んでるよ
I think I'm five or six arms short for all that.
腕の５ ６本は
足りないパターンだぜ
（パック）
うん だから まあ
余剰ダメージ分―
Yeah, the blue-haired maid took most of
the damage for you. She was in awful shape.
青髪のメイドの子も
ひどいありさまだったよ
Though, thanks to her demon
transformation, she heals really fast.
（パック）
もっとも あの子の場合は
鬼化の影響でガンガン治るからね
By the time she carried you back to
the village, she had no visible injuries.
村までスバルを担いで戻った時点で
目立った外傷はなかったよ
Don't give me a heart attack for no reason.
ムダにビビらせんなよ
Anyway, Rem went back to the village?
ともかく レムも
村に戻ってんだな
で 子供たちは？
呪いは解呪(かいじゅ)されたのか？
And what about the kids?
Was the curse removed?
No worries there.
それも安心
Betty and I took care of it, so all's well!
僕とベティーで
うまくやったから 問題なし
Your judgment was right on the mark!
スバルの判断は大正解だったよ
Clap, clap, clap.
パチ パチ パチ
（スバル）ハア…
Has Emilia been here all night?
エミリアは 一晩中ここに？
うん スバルの治療で
オドまで削って消耗してるから―
Yeah.
In order to heal you,
she drained her resources
right down to her odo,
so you should let her sleep.
寝かせておいてあげてくれる？
Balse, you're awake?
（ラム）
バルス 起きたのね
Ram...
あっ ラム
Listen, uh... I mean, about Rem...
なんつーか その…
レムのことは…
How shameless you are,
あれだけ重症だったのに―
pestering others for food so soon
after being gravely injured.
目が覚めたら すぐ食事を
せがむなんて浅ましい
Maybe some dog rubbed off
on you when they bit you.
犬に噛(か)まれて
犬がうつったんじゃないの？
How the heck does dog rub off?
犬がうつるってどんな状態だよ
Eat this.
（ラム）食らうがいいわ
（スバル）ん？
Huh?
Sofubozu!
Delicious, isn't it?
おいしいでしょ
I thought I was gonna die!
死ぬかと思ったわ！
うまかったけど
But yes, it was good!
It's freshly made. I mean...
できたて いえ―
Freshly steamed.
蒸(ふ)かしたてよ
Why do you look so proud of yourself!?
（スバル）
何だよ その決め顔！
Okay, okay.
はいはい もう１個あげるから
黙って むさぼっていなさい
You can have another,
so quiet down and eat it.
And well... As for last night,
you have my honest thanks.
まあ 昨夜の件に関しては
素直にお礼を言っておくわ
Good boy.
ご苦労様
"Good boy"? Always with
the condescending tone.
（スバル）
ご苦労様って
どこまでも上からだな
Was it really something
deserving of your thanks?
お前が礼を言うようなことか？
When a domain's people suffer
any loss, its lord is held liable.
（ラム）
領民に何か不利益があれば
領主の責が問われる
あのまま
ウルガルムの群れに―
Imagine the consequences if that pack of ulgarm
had further endangered those children.
子供たちが脅かされていたら
と思うと―
Your course of action was just.
バルスの行動は正解だったわ
Ulgarm?
ウルガルム？
あの黒い魔獣の名前か？
That's what those black witchfiends are called?
Yes, but don't worry about them.
ええ でも大丈夫―
I reconnected the broken barrier,
ほつれていた結界は
結び直したから 村の中は安全よ
so the village is safe.
I spent the night patrolling the barrier to ensure there were no more problems.
一晩かけて 結界に問題はないか
見て周ったから―
No ulgarm should be able to cross
it and enter the village.
境界を越えて村に入る
ウルガルムはいないはず
So you can relax.
だから安心しなさい
ベア子
Lil' Bea?
よう 子供たちの解呪
手伝ってくれたんだって？
Hey!
I heard you helped dispel
the curse from the kids.
Thanks.
ありがとな
No big deal.
（ベアトリス）別に
I suppose Betty only helped
at Bubby's request.
ベティーはただ にーちゃに
頼まれたからやっただけかしら
But we have more important matters to discuss.
それより 話があるのよ
What did you bring me all
the way out here to say?
わざわざ こんな所に連れてきて
何の用件だ？
In less than half a day,
あと半日もしないうちに
お前は死ぬかしら
I suppose you will die.
You don't look as disturbed as I expected.
思ったより
動じていないのよ
I suppose I thought you'd
start wailing and crying.
もっと ピーピー泣きわめくものと
思ったかしら
The curse still isn't lifted, then?
（スバル）
呪い まだ解呪できてないんだな
When the pack of witchfiends
attacked you in the forest,
森で魔獣の群れに
やられた時―
they planted another curse deep inside you.
追加でごっそり
植え付けられているのよ
Can I ask why this one can't be removed?
（スバル）
解けない呪いってのは
どういう理由か聞いていいか？
I suppose that's simple enough.
簡単な話かしら
Too many curses have been placed on you,
making it too complex to remove them all.
かけられた呪いが
重なりすぎて―
解くには 複雑になりすぎて
しまっているのよ
Too many curses?
（スバル）
呪いが重なってる？
When there's only one, removing it
is as simple as untying a knot.
呪いが１つなら たぐって
簡単にほどくこともできるかしら
But the curses on you are a complex
web of many threads,
でも お前にかけられた呪いは―
何本もの糸が 複雑に絡まり合い
もつれている状態なのよ
far too tangled to undo.
All right, I get why
it's too hard to undo now.
難易度高(たけ)えのは 何となく分かった
けど 何で半日なんだ？
But why half a day?
After half a day, witchfiends replenish
mana by activating their spells.
（ベアトリス）
半日もすれば 魔獣はマナを求めて
術式を発動するのよ
I suppose the curse they cast on
you drains the target's mana dry.
あの魔獣の呪いは 対象から
マナを奪うという呪いかしら
To put it another way,
you've been turned into witchfiend food.
つまりは お前は
魔獣のエサにされたのよ
So they attack people because they're hungry?
腹減ったから人を襲う か…
That's a wild animal for you.
So simple-minded!
さすがは野生動物　シンプルだ
I guess we should be thankful they
haven't gotten hungry before now.
あいつらの小腹が
今まですいてなかったことに―
感謝しなきゃだなあ
You...
（ベアトリス）お前…
（スバル）ん？
I suppose you aren't even afraid.
怖くないのかしら
I'm giving you a countdown
to the end of your life, you know.
ベティーのこれは
お前にとっての余命宣告なのよ
Well, sure, I'm scared.
そりゃ怖いよ
But I doubt you came here just
to tell me I'm going to die.
でも わざわざ死の宣告だけ
しにくるほど―
いじわるじゃない
と 俺はお前を見てるんだが？
I don't think you're that mean.
I suppose you're under
the impression you know me.
お前がベティーの何を
知っているっていうのかしら
If nothing else, I feel I've known you
four times longer than I really have.
少なくとも
お前が思ってる４倍は―
長いつきあいぐらいの感覚だな
You make no sense!
（ベアトリス）
意味が分からないのよ
But I suppose the fact is you have
a very low chance of being saved now.
でも 助かる可能性が
ずっと低いのは事実かしら
I can take it. Just tell me how low it is.
聞かせろよ
その極小の可能性ってやつを
We're talking about a spell
that makes a meal of you.
これは 術式を介した食事なのよ
If the diner in question were to die, I suppose it's only logical that the meal would be canceled.
食べる側が命を落としたなら
食事は中断するのが道理かしら
So that's how it is, huh?
そういうことか
All I have to do is kill
the things that cursed me.
俺の体に呪いをかけた奴を
倒せばいい
But there are way too many of them.
けど これじゃ数が多すぎる
That's why Bubby hasn't told
that silly girl about the curse.
（ベアトリス）
にーちゃが あの娘に呪いのことを
黙っているのも そのせいなのよ
Yeah, if Emilia knew, she'd definitely try
to do something unreasonable.
（スバル）確かにな
エミリアが知ったら
きっと無理するもんな
And while that makes me really happy,
それはすっげえうれしいけど
すげえ怖(こえ)えよ
it scares me even more.
Man, the difficulty got cranked right up to Hell.
難易度がマジ鬼がかっていやがる
とてもじゃねえけど無理だ
This is just plain impossible.
I might as well give up—
諦めるっきゃ…
So you're going to give up?
（レム）
だから諦めるんですか？
Is there no other way to save him?
助ける方法は ほかには…
I suppose your head must be hurting.
頭でも痛くなったかしら
それも無理ないのよ
That isn't surprising.
I suppose not.
（ベアトリス）それだけかしら
The rest is in your hands now.
あとは
お前に好きにするがいいのよ
I swear... I'll save you.
（レム）必ず 助けます
Don't tell me...
（スバル）まさか…
Where... is Rem?
レムは どこだ？
Lil' Bea... Beatrice, where is Rem!?
ベア子
ベアトリス レムはどこだ！
If you were in her position,
what do you suppose you'd do?
お前が同じ立場なら
どうするかしら
I can't ignore what you said just now.
（ラム）
今の話 聞き捨てなりません
Ram?
ラム
Beatrice-sama,
（ラム）ベアトリス様―
Rem didn't go to the forest alone, did she?
まさかレムは １人で森に
I... I have to do this alone.
レムが… レムが１人でやらなきゃ
No one else needs to get hurt anymore!
傷つくのはもう レムだけで十分
Why?
（スバル）どうしてだ
Why would Rem go to such lengths for me?
どうしてレムが 俺のために
そこまでしてくれる？
Hey, hold on!
ちょっと待てって
Let go of me, Balse!
（ラム）
離しなさいバルス！
Right now, I'm not calm enough to be kind!
今のラムは余裕がないから
優しくはできないわ
If you want to save Rem
レムを助けたきゃ―
and consider me a friend at all, hear me out!
ついでに俺のことを―
ちっとは仲間と思ってんなら
聞いてくれ！
Do you know where Rem is?
レムの居場所は分かるのか
If I use my clairvoyance, I will!
（ラム）
分かるわ ラムの千里眼を使えば
Clairvoyance?
（スバル）千里眼？
It's a power that allows me to see
（ラム）
ラムと波長の合う存在―
what the bugs and animals on
my wavelength are seeing.
虫や動物といった生き物と
視界を共有する力よ
Then they're like your security cameras?
（スバル）
そいつらの視界を使った
監視カメラみたいなもんか
Well, if we can use it to get to Rem, fine.
ともあれ それでレムと
合流できんなら上等だ
Next question, are you a combat maid?
んで お前って戦えるタイプの
メイドだったりする？
What does that even mean?
それはどういう意味での質問？
It means I'm going to the forest with you.
俺も一緒に
森に入るって意味だ
You're coming with me?
（ラム）
ついてくるつもり？
Yeah. I'm bound to drag
you down in a fight, though.
ああ 戦いになったら
俺は超 足引っ張るからな
ハア…
You're sadly mistaken if you expect
I can fight like Rem does in her demon form.
鬼化したレムと同じくらい
戦えるのを―
期待されているなら無理よ
You're twins, right?
（スバル）
お前ら 双子だよな
If Rem is a demon, aren't you a demon too?
レムが鬼ってことは
ラムも鬼ってことじゃねえのか
Unlike Rem, I'm hornless.
レムと違って
ラムはツノナシだから
I can only use a rather
extreme bit of wind magic.
少し過激に
風の魔法が使えるだけよ
Going to retrieve the younger sister
（ベアトリス）
姉妹の妹を連れ戻すってことは
自分の命を諦めるってことなのよ
is akin to giving up on your own life.
I suppose you do understand that?
お前はそれが
理解できているのかしら
Not quite. Let me correct you there.
ちょっと違(ちげ)えよ 訂正するぜ
Forming the habit of giving up because
you're used to dying is dumb.
死に慣れて諦めぐせなんて
くっだらねえ
Life is precious! You only get one!
命は大事だ １個しかない
When you guys went through so much
to save mine, I realized that.
お前らが必死こいて
つないでくれたから―
それが分かった
So if you don't mind, I'm going to
struggle to the bitter end.
だから みっともなく
あがかせてもらう
It's time to make a comeback!
逆転劇を起こそうぜ
I've bounced back from the
terrible state I was in.
あんだけひでえ状態から
ここまで持ち直したんだ
I'm a greedy guy.
欲張りな俺は 俺らしく―
And I want to see this story's
continuation, with me in it.
俺含めた後日談が
見たくてしょうがねえんだよ
Now, let's get moving to our grand finale!
さあ 最後の大勝負といこうぜ
Bring it on, Fate!
運命様 上等だ！
（スバル）ハア…
You gave a pretty heroic speech back there.
随分とかっこいいたんかを
切っていたけど―
But when I see you close to becoming
nothing but baggage,
いざ お荷物まっしぐらな姿を
目の当たりにすると―
it's difficult to hide my disappointment.
失望を隠すのに苦労するわ
I'm still recovering, so my energy
is spent, and I'm low on blood.
こっちは病み上がりで
体力浪費状態に―
血も足りてねえんだ
Oh, and I didn't get to hear
Emilia-tan say, "Take care."
そういえば エミリアたんに―
行ってらっしゃいって
言ってもらいそびれてる
まだ ただいまを
言ってないなら―
Until you say, "I'm home,"
last night's "Take care" is still in effect.
昨晩のいってらっしゃいが有効よ
I-Is that how it works?
そ… そういうもんかな…
それに エミリア様以外からなら
もらったでしょ
Besides, didn't you get something from
someone other than Emilia-sama?
ああ ステキなやつをな
Yeah, something really awesome.
Take this.
（青年団長）
こいつを持っていけ
It's the sharpest sword in the village.
村一番の業物だわ
Thanks, man.
あんがとよ
We're counting on you.
（青年）頼んだぞ
Subaru!
（子供Ａ）スバルー
（子供たち）スバル
Hey, you guys! You're up and around?
おお お前たち 目が覚めたのか
Where are you going?
（子供Ｂ）どこ行くの？
Back into the forest?
（ペトラ）
また森に入るの？
Don't go back there, Subaru!
（リュカ）
もう行っちゃやだよ スバル
I'll be fine. Don't worry.
大丈夫だ 心配すんな
どこにも行かねえよ
I'm not going anywhere.
What's the sword for?
（ミルド）その剣は何？
This?
これ？
It's a thank you gift from all of us.
それはお礼だ みんなからの
I wanna thank you too!
（ペトラ）私もお礼する！
Hey!
ああ こら
You can have this!
And this!
お菓子ときれいな石
Candy, a pretty stone...
And...
あと ほかは…
There was a freaking bug in there!
虫 入ってやがった！
どさくさに紛れて
とんでもねえクソガキどもだ
Damn brats, sneaking that
in while I was distracted!
I'll give them a good scolding later!
あとで説教したる
It's just proof that they admire you.
慕われてる証拠でしょ
I wonder what they see in a man like you.
どこがいいのかしら こんな男
子供の純真な瞳には―
In a child's pure eyes,
my true, manly nature shines through.
俺という男の本質が
きらめいて見えるんだよ
それに 好かれてるのは
俺ばっかりじゃねえ
Also, I'm not the only one they like.
You could tell, right?
ラムにも分かっただろ？
そうね
I suppose so.
Take this too!
Hey! Why did you put dirt in there?
何だ？ こら
なに 土なんかいれてんだ
Just accept it!
（ペトラ）ラムちー
Ram-chi!
レムりんにもお礼言いたいから
あとで連れてきてね
We also want to thank
Rem-rin, so bring her later!
Promise, Ram-chi!
絶対ね ラムちー
バルス 千里眼を使うわ
少し待ちなさい
Balse, I'm going to use my clairvoyance.
Wait a moment.
Balse, something is watching us right now.
バルス ラムたちを
見ている視界があるわ
なに？
What?
Up there.
（ラム）あっちよ
（スバル）どこ？
Where?
Don't relax yet. More are coming.
（ラム）まだよ 次が来るわ
Hey! D-Don't walk off without me!
って… サラっと行くなよ
Anyway, why is it that everything
under the sun loses its head around you?
（ラム）それにしても―
どうして どの個体も
バルスを見たとたんに―
冷静さを失うのかしら
ふに落ちないわ
I don't understand.
やっぱり弱そうだから？
Because you seem so weak?
After all that hesitation,
that's your conclusion?
悩んで出た結論がそれ？ 失敬な
How rude!
じゃあ チョロそうだから？
Then, perhaps it's because you seem like a wimp.
根本的な部分が
変わってませんよねーえ
That doesn't change the root
of what you're saying, big sis!
お姉様ーあ
Hey, can I ask what that "hornless"
thing you mentioned means?
なあ さっき言ってた―
“ツノナシ”って
何か聞いていいか
別に
Nothing special.
Just as it sounds,
聞いたまま
it's another name for a foolish
demon that lost its horn.
鬼のくせに角をなくした
愚物に与えられる別称よ
ちょっとした いざこざで―
I got into a bit of trouble
and lost my only horn.
１本しかなかった角をなくしたのよ
以来 何事もレムを
頼ることにしているわ
Ever since, I've relied on Rem for everything.
I guess I shouldn't have asked, huh?
たぶん 悪いこと聞いたよな
なぜ？
Why?
Well, I don't know how important horns
are to the race you call "demons,"
あっ いや
鬼って種族にとって―
角がどんだけのもんなのかは
知らないけど―
予想じゃ
かなり大きな問題だろ？
but I assume it's a pretty serious problem.
それに 結構無神経に
触ったかなと思って
I just thought asking about it
might have been insensitive.
Back then was one thing,
but now, it doesn't bother me.
（ラム）
当時はともかく
今は落ち着いているわ
角をなくしたことで
得たものも拾えた命もある
By losing my horn, there are things
I've gained and lives I've saved.
もっとも レムはそう思っては
いないでしょうけど
I'm sure Rem doesn't see it that way, though.
Huh?
（ラム）
元来 鬼族は２本の角を持っている
In most cases, members of
the demon race have two horns,
けれど 双子はその角を最初から
１本欠損して生まれてくるの
but twins are born with just one horn each.
だから 双子は忌み嫌われ―
That's why twins are detested.
And it's customary to dispose of
them immediately after birth.
生まれた直後に
処分されるのが習わし
でも ラムたちは生かされた
But Rem and I were allowed to live.
A demon's horns awaken its demon instincts,
鬼族の角は 鬼としての
本能を呼び覚まし―
周囲のマナを食らい尽くして
戦闘能力を高める器官なの
allowing it to devour mana,
heightening combat ability.
でも ムチャをすれば
その反動でボロボロに傷つく
But if used haphazardly,
the backlash can be devastating.
I don't want to see Rem like that.
（ラム）
そんなレムを見たくない
（スバル）
レムが大事で心配か？
Are you worried because you care for Rem?
当たり前でしょ 確かに
あの子のほうがラムより強い
Of course I am.
It's true that she is stronger than I am,
but that's no reason not to worry about her.
でも それは心配しない
理由にはならないわ
No matter the order given,
she does it far better.
何をやらせても
あの子のほうがずっと上
でもラムは
あの子の姉様だもの
But I'm still her older sister.
I'll never back down on that.
その立場だけは
絶対に揺るがない
Okay, I get it.
分かった　俺に考えがある
I've got a hunch.
だから心配すんな
レムは必ず 無事連れて帰る
So don't worry.
We'll bring Rem back safe and sound!
（スバル）
俺の考えが正しければ きっと来る
If my hunch is right, they're sure to come.
死に戻りのことを伝えようとすれば
それに誘われて
They'll be drawn here by my attempt
to tell her about Return by Death.
Ram, the thing is, I can Retur—
ラム 俺 実は死に…
What's that?
（ラム）何？
（スバル）くっ…
ハッハハ…
I made a wager that came with a bit of pain.
ちょいとばかり
痛みを伴う賭けに出てみた
（ラム）
何をしたの バルス
What did you do, Balse?
The wind is erratic,
and I smell beasts growing nearer.
風が乱れて 獣臭が近づいてくる
それもすごい数
A lot of them, at that.
レムはまだ見つからないのに
And we haven't found Rem yet!
まあ 安心しろよ
Well, don't worry.
Something tells me we'll cross paths soon.
たぶん そう遠くないうちに
合流できるから
（ラム）
どうして そう言い切れるの？
What makes you say that?
（スバル）ずばり―
Because of the witch's lingering scent!
魔女の残り香だ
Rem's goal is to hunt down
all the witchfiends, right?
（スバル）
レムの目的は
魔獣を狩り尽くすことだろ
その魔獣たちは 魔女の
残り香に誘われて―
The witchfiends will be drawn
to the witch's scent,
and come right to me.
俺をめがけて食らいついてくる
Then Rem will have no choice
but to follow them toward me.
そしたら 魔獣を追って
レムも俺の所に来ざるを得ない
I call it "Operation:
Natsuki Subaru is the Bait"!
名付けて
ナツキ･スバル おとり大作戦だ
んじゃ 戦いに関しては
超お前頼りなんで―
Okay, I'm gonna have to rely on
you to fight, so go for it.
そこんとこ よろしく
When this is over, I'll make you look
objectively at what you just said,
あとで 客観的に自分が
何を言ってるのか 振り返って―
until you wish you were dead!
死にたくなりなさい！
This is what I get for believing you
when you said you could fight!
（スバル）
戦えるって言うから
信頼したら これだよ！
（ラム）
戦えていたでしょう 実際
Well, I did fight, didn't I?
My strength just didn't hold out
as long as I thought it would.
思ったより ラムの体力が
もたなかっただけで
Damn it!
（スバル）クッソー！
うわ しまっ…
Crap!
D-Damn it all!
クッソ だらーっ！！
We were almost dead meat there...
危うく ご愁傷様するとこだったぜ
If we fall, we'll both be in trouble.
（ラム）
落ちたら さすがに
２人とも危ないわよ
Balse, can you climb up?
バルス 登れるの？
I'd love to make it up by sheer willpower,
根性でどうにかしたいが
上で待ち構えている魔獣が問題に…
but the witchfiends waiting
up there are a problem—
うっ うわっ 業物がー！
The sharpest sword!
（ラム）エルフーラ
El Fula!
（スバル）
とっと とーっとっ…
That was too close for comfort...
あっぶねー…
No kidding, Ram-sama
had the timing of Buddha.
マジで ラム様仏様のタイミング
あれ？ おいラム
Huh? Hey, Ram?
H-Hey!
おい！
チクショウ ウソだろ
Damn it. You can't be serious.
Shit, this timing couldn't be worse...
クッソ… タイミング
悪すぎるぞ 俺
Rem!
レム！
Thank goodness you're safe!
無事だったのかよ
We're saved.
助かった
Damn it.
クッソー 鬼化したはいいけど
制御できない設定か
She can turn into a demon,
but she can't control it?
Hey, Rem! My name is Natsuki Subaru!
おい レム 俺の名前は
ナツキ･スバル！
天地無用の雑用見習い
A completely useless trainee in odd jobs...
Uh, I mean, the Roswaal mansion's
most promising servant!
ロズワール邸の期待の下男
I've made tons of problems
for you and Ram,
お前やラムには
迷惑掛け倒しだったが―
but we've been friends at times,
それでも 時に仲よく 時に…
and fought at others—
話の途中で撲殺とか
しつけがなってねえぞ
Trying to beat me to death while
I'm still talking is pretty rude!
Now's my chance.
（スバル）今のうちに…
クソ ダメだ 見過ごせねえ
Damn, I can't do it! I can't ignore her!
Take the plunge, Subaru.
踏み切れ 俺
男は度胸 女は愛嬌(きょう)だ
Men are about guts,
and women are about beauty!
So...
だから―
Quit making that scary face,
and put on a smile, Rem!
怖い顔しねえで笑え レム！
俺は死にも…
I can Return by—
Her horn...
（ラム）角よ
You're awake?
目 覚めたのか
That should have been the perfect moment.
（ラム）
今が一番 おいしいタイミングだと
思ったのよ
You have good intuition, big sis!
（スバル）
いい勘してるぜ お姉様
What about her horn?
角って言ったか？
It's the horn that's making Rem a demon.
（ラム）
レムを鬼たらしめているのは
あの角だから
一発 強烈なのをたたき込めば
それで戻ってくる
One good, solid hit should
bring her back to normal.
（スバル）確かか？
You're sure?
I am. I think. I hope.
（ラム）
はず きっと
だといいと思うわ
How confident!
（スバル）曖昧なのな
A hit to that one spot.
あそこに１発って
無理くさくね？
Doesn't it seem impossible?
知恵と勇気を振り絞って
どうにかしなさい
Muster up some courage
and put your brain to use.
Well, I do have one idea
for what we could do,
どうにかできそうな方法は
実は思い浮かんでんだけど―
but I know it'll make you mad.
きっと お前は怒るし…
If it'll bring my sister back to
her senses, I won't get mad.
それで妹が正気に戻るなら
ラムは怒ったりしないわ
Really?
（スバル）本当に？
Absolutely.
（ラム）本当の本当に
You swear to Roscchi?
（スバル）
ロズっちに誓って？
（ラム）
そこを選ぶとは命知らずね
That's the most ill-advised
name you could have chosen.
Yes, I swear to Roswaal-sama.
ええ ロズワール様に誓って
All right!
（スバル）よーし
Heave...
Ho!
（ラム）痛っ
（スバル）
ビビっちまった
あと一歩 勇気が足りんかった
I choked!
I didn't have the guts for that last step!
If I let this chance slip by,
I won't have another!
（スバル）
ここを逃せば もう先は無い
笑え レム！
Smile, Rem!
今日の俺は鬼より―
Today, I'm demoniacally possessed for real!
鬼がかってるぜー！
Demoniacally Possessed  Methods
oh,
please
don't
let
me
die
Demoniacally Possessed  Methods
oh,